'Citrine framework' uses XML as the programming language.
So, you can make high quality applications easily!
Let's see samples!
The first thing is about the transition effect.
The 'NAVIGATIONCONTAINER' provides many transition effects.
This is flip effect.
door effect.
and mosaic.
If you want to change the effect,
just change the transitionIn/OutEffect attribute of the VIEWITEM element.
then, build and run application.
Now, you can see the different effect.
Next section is about the animation effect.
Let's see animation effect sample!
The background moves to the right.
The ship moves on the lake.
This is another sample
scaling,
showing
rotaing
and frame animation.
The citrine framework includes various componenets as a default.
You can change UI object and style easily.
This is 'GALLERY' UI object.
You can see the 'dot' on the bottom.
Let's change the style from 'dot' to 'thumbnail'.
And run application.
It's 'GALLERY' UI object with 'thumbnail' style.
You can also change the style by replacing to the similar UI object.
Let's change the 'GALLERY' UI object to the 'COVERFLOW'.
And run application.
Now, you can see the 'COVERFLOW'.
The citrine framework provides the screen rotation effect.
Some device does not have any screen rotation effect.
but, you can emulate the screen rotation effect.
Next section is about the 'Theme'.
This is a sample of the basic android UI controls.
If you want iOS style, define a new 'theme xml'.
By changing a single theme attribute,
you can change the whole application UI.
The citrine framework provides real dpi.
You can use the real size on any devices.
This is a battery image.
If you use the 'cm' unit for the layout values,
you can get the exact same size as the real size.
The final section is a tip about the updating resource.
The citrine framework supprots the http protocol.
You don't need to rebuild. just refresh.
Thank you.
This sample was made from MOML(Mobile Object Markup Language) that allows you to easily build functional, native application for mobile device.
The MOML library is free, and doesn't require you to know the details of how the mobile device builds its views.